let questions21 = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "accustomed",
      answer: "C. gewöhnt",
      options: [
        "A. fremd",
        "B. erschöpft",
        "C. gewöhnt",
        "D. aufgeregt"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "to affirm",
      answer: "A. bestätigen",
      options: [
        "A. bestätigen",
        "B. tanzen",
        "C. kochen",
        "D. schlafen"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "astonished",
      answer: "D. erstaunt",
      options: [
        "A. müde",
        "B. hungrig",
        "C. wütend",
        "D. erstaunt"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "to bang",
      answer: "B. schlagen",
      options: [
        "A. flüstern",
        "B. schlagen",
        "C. schwimmen",
        "D. lächeln"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "clan",
      answer: "C. Sippe",
      options: [
        "A. Gebäude",
        "B. Fahrzeug",
        "C. Sippe",
        "D. Werkzeug"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "dim",
      answer: "A. dunkel",
      options: [
        "A. dunkel",
        "B. schnell",
        "C. schwer",
        "D. laut"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "emphasis",
      answer: "D. Betonung",
      options: [
        "A. Farbe",
        "B. Geschmack",
        "C. Größe",
        "D. Betonung"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "fable",
      answer: "B. Märchen",
      options: [
        "A. Rechnung",
        "B. Märchen",
        "C. Werkzeug",
        "D. Fahrkarte"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "feast",
      answer: "C. Festmahl",
      options: [
        "A. Sportart",
        "B. Krankheit",
        "C. Festmahl",
        "D. Fahrzeug"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "to glow",
      answer: "A. glühen",
      options: [
        "A. glühen",
        "B. rennen",
        "C. waschen",
        "D. pflanzen"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 11,
      question: "hollow",
      answer: "D. hohl",
      options: [
        "A. nass",
        "B. stark",
        "C. süß",
        "D. hohl"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 12,
      question: "instinct",
      answer: "B. Instinkt",
      options: [
        "A. Möbel",
        "B. Instinkt",
        "C. Maschine",
        "D. Gebäude"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 13,
      question: "joint",
      answer: "C. Gelenk",
      options: [
        "A. Getränk",
        "B. Pflanze",
        "C. Gelenk",
        "D. Kleidung"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 14,
      question: "to leak",
      answer: "A. lecken",
      options: [
        "A. lecken",
        "B. singen",
        "C. malen",
        "D. fliegen"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 15,
      question: "physician",
      answer: "D. Arzt",
      options: [
        "A. Bäcker",
        "B. Maler",
        "C. Gärtner",
        "D. Arzt"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 16,
      question: "to sacrifice",
      answer: "B. opfern",
      options: [
        "A. spielen",
        "B. opfern",
        "C. reisen",
        "D. lernen"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 17,
      question: "stiff",
      answer: "C. steif",
      options: [
        "A. weich",
        "B. leicht",
        "C. steif",
        "D. warm"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 18,
      question: "to stroke",
      answer: "A. streicheln",
      options: [
        "A. streicheln",
        "B. springen",
        "C. backen",
        "D. rechnen"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 19,
      question: "tragic",
      answer: "D. tragisch",
      options: [
        "A. lustig",
        "B. hektisch",
        "C. kraftvoll",
        "D. tragisch"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 20,
      question: "tune",
      answer: "B. Melodie",
      options: [
        "A. Buch",
        "B. Melodie",
        "C. Tisch",
        "D. Fenster"
      ]
    }
];

export default questions21;